yes beneath comes i hailnight we are she Jack of g's
odd
peace you draw peach are true shimmer
yes sonic comes a Halo
night be a poor
you're the reason
to you yeah come on
你叫许郎肮脏
你叫参察
要出上你他娘啊你no long true
yes she's a godnigga says
hang on earth to suddenly plenty and into his heart
hungry acts so good old
na na na
na na
耶稣尼康萨也有night we sleep
家雅济萨
all through my wounded by one at dawn silent peach true
yesterday comes hanging on
like we have all
you're really timeto you yeah come moon
negative long long talk
negative time tell you to show me
China gagy moon true
yes she threw them naked sweats and you'll be true
someday young tea and into his heart
yes of it all
na na na na
time you're not in all i won't you
yes if Jah godnigga says
hang your way to someday come see i'm in true it's hard
i am
那一年
那一年国王之上东南